http://www.lifesaving.org/member-services/policies-procedures/right-to-privacy

Right to Privacy
Personal Information Collected by the Lifesaving Society:
By participating in any Lifesaving Society Leadership program or by accessing any of the Society’s services, there is an implied consent to the Society collecting personal information. Candidate information collected on Society Test Sheets and Rosters is required for the administration of Lifesaving Society programs. The personal information  collected may include Member ID, gender, date of birth, phone number, street address and e-mail address. These are recorded in the Member Management System.
The personal information collected will not be released to third parties unless authorized by the member. The personal information collected will not be used for any purpose other than the administration and delivery of the Society’s programs and services.
The Lifesaving Society shares important member communications such as leadership training opportunities as well as information related to our programs, lifesaving sport, member services, safety management and public education with our members through electronic communications (i.e. Ripples and Communiques).
It is the Lifesaving Society’s practice to provide our Affiliate members with a current listing of Lifesaving Society leadership volunteers, upon request, which includes the phone number, mailing and e-mail address. The purpose is to provide Affiliate members with a list of individuals they can contact directly for their program delivery and service needs.
Please contact the Lifesaving Society directly if you do not want your personal information to be included in the current listing of Lifesaving Society leadership volunteers available to Affiliate members to access for their program delivery and service needs.
